# Doug Watro

DougWatro@gmail.com

DougWatro.com

631-681-0941

# LANGUAGES

C + +

**C**#

JAVA

HTML5

CSS / SASS

JAVASCRIPT / ES6

# **SKILLS**

GAME DEVELOPMENT
SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT
OOP

DATA STRUCTURES

CODE OPTIMIZATION

ANDROID APP DEVELOPMENT

**UX DESIGN** 

WEB DESIGN / SEO

FULL STACK WEB DEV

# SOFTWARE / FRAMEWORKS

UNREAL ENGINE / UNITY

VISUAL STUDIOS

GIT / SLACK / TRELLO

ANDROID STUDIO

REACT / REDUX

BOOTSTRAP

EXPRESS / NODEJS

MONGODB

ADOBE CC

# GOALS

Create interactive experiences that provided a service or entertain many different people.

Work together with great, passionate minds to create even greater things.

Expand my knowledge and become a seasoned professional in the software, game design, or entertainment industry.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **DESIGN ASSISTANT | MAGIC SPELL STUDIOS**

FEBRUARY 2014 - AUGUST 2014

Conceptualized and designed 3D game levels to be integrated within a larger game world. Work among a team of 20 to design the overall direction of the project. Designed small levels to be used in promotional material.

# LEVEL DESIGNER/3D ARTIST | IGM GRAD DEPARTMENT

WINTER - SPRING 2015

Worked with a team of grad students to assist them in completing their capstone project. Acted as the sole level designer for their 3D topdown action tower defense game. Worked with other artist to model and texture assets when needed.

# INDECISION BETA APP RELEASE | GOOGLE PLAY STORE

LATE 2016 - EARLY 2017

Designed, programmed, and began public beta tests of an Android App on the Google Play Store.

# **EDUCATION**

ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2012 - PRESENT BS | GAME DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT